#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ishanvohra2 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

C++

Java

#### Honors-Awards

National Children's Science Congress - 2016 (State Level)

National Children's Science Congress - 2017 (National Level)

India International Innovation Fair 2017 (Bronze Medal)

India International Innovation Fair 2018 (National Medal)

Selected in Top 30 Innovations by Atal Innovation Mission

# Ishan V.

Central

### Summary

I am 19 year old entrepreneur. I am working on a start up company which helps small businesses and startups to build their applications and websites in India. My skills include programming, light video editing and game development. I don't only like to code but to create new things, that's what drives me. I have worked on various projects.

Also, I have been mentoring students of my college in Game Development since past few months.

### Experience

#### Microsoft

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador January 2020 - Present (8 months)

- Host events, workshops, and hackathons about Microsoft technologies like Azure, Sway etc. on campus
- Build and grow a community of students on-campus and online
- To acquire tools and training to lead technology discussions on campus
- To inform students about student benefits like Azure credits
- To work closely with Microsoft and other Student Ambassadors and build networks

Incubate IND Fellowship July 2020 - Present (2 months)

The Indie Corp Founder May 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months) New Delhi Area, India

International Organization Of Software Developers Game Development Mentor October 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months) Intellify
Android Developer
December 2019 - March 2020 (4 months)

## Education

Maharaja Surajmal Institute Of Technology

BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Information Technology · (2018 - 2022)

Modern Public School

Computer Programming/Programmer, General · (2016 - 2018)